(radio tuning)
(DJ) ...ninth inning
and a walk-off home run.
Game 3 of the series
is this coming Tuesday.
Now for a quick look
at the weather.
It was another hot one today
here in Dylan.
But it’s looking like another
beautiful evening tonight,
with an overnight low of 71°.
All right, party people,
summer’s now
officially dead ahead
with the annual rodeo
coming up next weekend.
Tickets still available
at the fairgrounds box office.
But keep it right here
for a chance to win
a pair of tickets
in the next hour.
Until then, here’s
the latest from The Killers.
Will this be
the song of the summer?
Stay tuned and stay cool.
("When You Were Young" playing)
♪ You sit there
In your heartache ♪
♪ Waiting on
Some beautiful boy to ♪
♪ To save you
From your old ways ♪
♪ You play forgiveness ♪
♪ Watch it now
Here he comes ♪
♪ He doesn’t look a thing
Like Jesus ♪
♪ But he talks
Like a gentleman ♪
♪ Like you imagined
When you were young ♪
(Jonah) I’m on empty.
I got to fill up, right?
(man speaking indistinctly)
(Morgan) I want some, uh...
some of those salty straws.
You want what?
(Jenny chuckles)
So who’s gonna buy
the beer tonight?
Oh, not me.
Not it! Ha!
Okay, I guess
I’ll give it a try.
(Jenny) You’re gonna
do great, babe.
The glasses...
They make you look mature.
All right. I’ll be quick.
(Morgan) Jonah, hold up.
I need to pee anyway,
so I’ll come with you.
(song fades)
♪ When you were young ♪
Thanks.
(softly) Yep.
(billing machine beeping)
("Fast Blood" playing)
(song continues playing)
(indistinct chattering)
♪ Good night
It’s stroke time ♪
♪ Let’s get paralyzed ♪
♪ Down both sides ♪
(song continues playing)
I agree.
Have a shot.
No, thank you.
Come on,
don’t be such a bore.
Well, that’s my job.
I’m the designated bore tonight.
All right. I guess I’ll just have
to have fun all by my lonesome.
What are you saying?
I’m only fun if I’m drunk?
Of course you’re fun.
Just, you know... drunk Morgan
is my favorite Morgan.
Chris Grant! Chris Grant!
We need our champion back here!
(girl) Come on, Jenny!
(Hank) We need you!
(girl clapping) Come on, Jenny!
(Chris)
Yo, Hank, we’re coming.
You have to come.
I need you. I’m right behind you on that.
Come on!
(Chris) Yo! Hey! Rack it up!
How did we both end up
with our exact opposites?
(people cheering)
Come on! Come on.
Oh, shoot!
Hey, Jonah.
Um...
My sister has it in her head
that tonight’s
the night for...
Oh, no. (chuckles)
I... I have no intention
of doing that tonight.
You have my word.
Thank you. (chuckles)
(Chris) Morgan!
Come on!
You’re up!
Your shot!
Hey, sis!
Come on!
I’m just not in the mood
to drink tonight.
Me neither. It’s Pepsi.
Oh, thank you. (chuckles)
He didn’t mean
what he said.
He’s drunk.
You know how he gets.
Mmm. He’s probably right.
He’s not.
There’s no version of you
that’s boring.
I’m pregnant.
(fireworks exploding)
(people exclaiming)
(exhales)
(Jonah) All right, buddy.
Was that fun?
(Jenny)
Oh, there’s our little guy.
Okay.
Was that fun?
Yeah, he’s good.
(car door closes)
(Jonah) You okay?
(Jenny) Do you want to go
and see your auntie?
She’s the birthday girl.
(Jonah) Okay.
(Jenny) Look who it is!
Oh, my gosh. Hi.
Get out of there!
Stop doing dishes
on your birthday.
Take the baby.
Who’s my favorite nephew?
Hi.
You know, it’s bad enough you
make your own cake every year.
Well, someone else could learn
how to do it, in theory.
I’m just sayin’... Stop judging,
Mother Morgan. Get out of here.
I guess I raised you right.
I just never thought of you
as a dish-doing kind of gal.
(Jenny) Mm-hmm.
Okay, grill’s fixed.
Yeah? Thank you.
Ready when you are.
Thank you.
Look who I have!
Hi! Hey, little fella.
Hello!
You ready to party?
Always.
Of course you are.
Oh, you’re the sweetest guy.
Hi there.
Hey. Hi.
We’re just waiting on Clara.
She’s supposed to be home by 5:00.
I’m sure her rehearsal
just ran late. Want a beer?
No. No, thank you.
It’s your birthday, relax.
I know, I’m very relaxed.
Jen?
Yes, please. Thank you.
Pumping and dumping.
(chuckles)
(door hinge squeaks)
Hey.
What’s up, bud?
What’s up, man?
Beer?
Ah, I’m good.
You need some help?
Uh, do you want to dry?
Yeah.
Oh, actually,
I have a job for one of you,
which is that this guy
just unleashed...
(Jenny) Oh!
...something incredible
into his diaper.
I got it. Come here.
Ooh, that is stinky, dude!
Aww...
Thanks, Daddy.
Be right back.
Okay, if Clara’s not back soon,
we start without her.
Yeah, right.
Sounded good, right?
Oh, my God, yes!
Laying down the law.
I love it, babe.
(door hinge squeaking)
Oh, I hate that door.
So, hey.
Hey.
Jonah and I decided
to get married.
He proposed?
Uh, well, I mean,
no, not exactly. It was...
It was... a discussion.
It makes sense for it
to be our next move.
Well, that’s romantic.
Yeah. I’ll do that.
Okay.
I’m sorry,
your proposal was better?
No, but that’s
what I’m saying.
Except you knew this guy
in high school
and then you didn’t see him
for a gazillion years
then you slept together once
at his dad’s funeral?
We used to date.
I mean, we’ve like... (scoffs)
We’ve known each other forever.
You dated for a month
all those years ago.
I mean, it’s just...
(Jenny) What?
Morgan,
we have a baby together.
Isn’t that the same reason
that you and Chris got married?
I mean...
can’t you just
be happy for me?
I’m sorry.
Yes. Of course.
Of course I am.
Congratulations. This is...
It’s really exciting.
Thank you.
Okay.
I’ll be a good maid of honor.
Promise.
(chuckles)
Where is Clara?
(Clara singing along to stereo)
♪ Wish I could do.. What I’m told ♪
♪ Aw, no ♪
♪ Dad’s on the phone
And he’s lecturing me ♪
♪ ’Bout a girl that he met
Back when he was 19 ♪
♪ It’s never gonna work ’cause
The puzzle won’t piece... ♪
(cell phone ringing)
What? That’s the best part.
Come on.
(music continues playing
over car stereo)
(continues singing along)
♪ Son of a gun ♪
♪ But I know that he’s right♪
♪ ’Cause the girl that I love
Never treated me right ♪
♪ Writing’s on the wall
I pretend I can’t read ♪
Shit. Don’t turn around, Clara.
♪ You’re forgetting me ♪
♪ Losing my patience ♪
♪ Confusing the waitress ♪
Hmm.
♪ She said, "Honey
You’ll be all right" ♪ (grunting)
♪ But she gets paid
To be nice♪
♪ Ah, hell, Dad’s on the phone
And he’s lecturing me ♪
♪ ’Bout a girl that he met
Back when he was 19 ♪
♪ It’s never gonna work ’cause
The puzzle won’t piece... ♪
(Miller) Hey, Clara.
(song stops playing)
You burying bodies out here?
That’s exactly
what I’m doing, yeah.
Come here a sec.
Look, I stopped
to offer you a ride,
not get involved in whatever
shady shit you’re up to.
(grunting)
What are you doing?
I’ll show you. Come here.
Look, it’s my mom’s birthday
and I’m already running late.
Okay, then hurry up.
Before I get caught.
(chuckles)
God. These shoes
aren’t meant for this.
Those aren’t shoes.
Stealing the city limit sign?
(grunts)
Nope, just moving it.
(groans)
Can you grab that end?
(sighs)
Giving you a ride
is one thing,
being your accomplice
is another.
(sighs)
(sign clanks)
(cattle lowing)
(sighs)
Why are we doing this again?
Okay, so my gramps,
he can’t get out much.
And Roman’s Pizza
doesn’t deliver
outside of city limits,
so...
I’ve been coming out here
every day
moving this sign
little by little where no one notices.
Breaking the law for pizza?
It’s really good pizza.
(chuckles)
Shit.
You okay? Oh.
I’ll buy you some new ones.
(sighs)
All right, perfect.
I’ll take that ride now.
(pop song playing over radio)
(Miller) Whoa, all A’s?
Do you study a lot
or does it come natural?
A little bit of both.
You always this nosy?
Sorry, only child syndrome.
Yeah. I’m an only child.
You don’t see me rifling
through your pockets.
Do you want to rifle
through my pockets?
My mom would flip if she knew
how serious I was about acting.
She thinks I’m only
gonna apply to State.
You applied anywhere?
Uh, my gramps is insisting
I apply to UNCSA.
But 100K in student loan debt
for a film degree
is, like,
horror-movie scary, so...
UNCSA is my first pick
for drama school.
Yeah?
Yeah, you want to go
to film school there?
Uh...
(cell phone buzzes)
Uh, hey, babe. Um...
Nah, I was just
on a walk home
and I got hot
so I caught a ride.
Just some dude, I don’t know.
Yeah, yeah,
I’ll talk to you later.
Okay. Bye.
"Just some dude"?
Now who’s being nosy?
(horse neighs)
(goat bleating)
Not what you were expecting?
No, I was just...
My wallet’s inside.
You know, to pay for
those things you call shoes.
So, do you always
lie to your girlfriend?
(chuckles)
Well, if it saves me
from a three-hour
interrogation, yeah.
Sounds like a super
healthy relationship.
That’s Gramps.
Hmm.
(grunts)
(drawer thuds)
Okay, look.
If those cost
more than ten bucks,
you’ve been ripped off.
I don’t--
Okay. I’ve got a job.
Take the money.
I don’t actually expect you--
Pleasure doing business
with you.
Guess you weren’t kidding
about film school.
Why would I kid about that?
I don’t know.
Me wanting to be an actress
can sound kind of silly
sometimes.
I don’t think so.
(cell phone buzzing)
I think that’s
this dude’s cue to leave.
Oh, hey, Gramps.
You take your meds?
Every damn day since your
grandma skipped out on me.
Yeah, Grandma didn’t skip town.
She died of a heart attack.
Yeah, well,
either way, she left me
and I’ll never
forgive her for it.
Mmm...
Hey, now come on!
Those don’t grow on trees!
Yeah, and neither do lungs.
So...
Did I not teach you manners?
Introduce me, damn it.
Yeah, um...
Oh, uh... Hi. Clara.
This is...
Clara,
a friend from school.
Clara, this is
my very grumpy gramps.
Hi.Don’t listen to him.
Who is this? Who are you?
That’s Charlie.
Charles if he misbehaves.
Clara, huh?
Clara... Clara Grant, hmm?
Yeah. How did you know?
Hey, Clara Grant,
would you tell my grandson
that if he breaks
another one of my cigarettes,
I’m rescinding his inheritance?
(Clara and Miller chuckle)
Yeah, go ahead.
You said the only thing
you have of any value is air.
Yeah, air which
you will not be inheriting.
Mmm...
I get my charm from him.
(chuckles)
Clara, would you like to hear
some Miller stories?
I got plenty of them.
(laughs) Absolutely.
Well, that’s--
(Gramps) Once when Miller
was six years old,
he pooped his pants
in a grocery store
because the automatic flushers
on the public toilets terrified him.
Okay. Let’s go, come on.
(Gramps) Wait, wait,
I got another one!
When he was 15--
I got video--
We went to a school play,
wasn’t it?
Remember that?
Oh, no. Okay.
Thank you, Gramps. Let’s go.
No, please, I want to see.
(Gramps) All right,
you come back any time!
Bye! What play?
Okay, don’t mind him.
He’s old and confused.
No, I don’t know,
once you finish your city limits mission,
I might just have to order
a pepperoni-and-pineapple
and get Gramps to tell me
embarrassing
Miller Adams stories.
Pineapple on pizza?
Mm-hmm...
You’re not welcome here.
(Clara chuckles)
(Miller chuckles)
("Just You" playing)
You can go
call your girlfriend now.
See you at school, Clara.
♪ Sun’s set♪
♪ I’ve waited for you
All day ♪ (phone chimes)
All day ♪
♪ My love ♪
(singer vocalizing)
♪ Just you, just you
Just you, just you ♪
(song ends)
(muffled men chattering)
Jenny.
Just wait, okay?
It’s coming together.
(cell phone ringing)
Ah!
Hey, Clare Bear.
What’s up? Your mom tried
calling you. Where are you?
Yeah. Sorry, I know--
rehearsal ran long.
I’ve got to grab Lexie still.
Am I on speaker?
No. Of course not.
(imperceptible)
Guess who just
spent the last half hour
with the coolest guy in school.
Oh, my God.
Really?
(mouths)
Mm-hmm. I helped him move
a city limits sign-- don’t ask.
And I gave him a ride home.
We hung out in his bedroom.
And now he’s following me.
(mouths) Bedroom!
That’s so exciting.
(Clara) Yeah.
Should I follow him back?
I mean, he told his girlfriend
that "some dude"
gave him a ride home, so...
clearly they’ve got
a messed-up thing going on.
Wait, he has a girlfriend?
(Clara) Yeah.
Yeah, she graduated last year.
No, um, don’t do that.
You have to stay away,
Clare Bear. He’s taken.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, listen,
don’t tell my mom about this.
You know how she gets.
Yeah. No, of course I won’t.
Don’t worry.
Okay, see you soon.
(Clara) Bye.
Sometimes it scares me
how good of a liar you are.
Well... boo!
(Morgan chuckles)
You want some?
(Morgan) Stop! No!
(Chris) Lexie, can you hand me
some more of those chips?
(Lexie) Yes.
(Chris) Thanks.
(chuckles)
(baby exclaims)
(Clara gasps)
(Jonah) What is that?
What is that, dude?
(Jonah chuckles)
Lexie, phone down.
It’s my Tinder date,
Mr. Grant.
Don’t you have to be 18
to be on that app?
I am 18...
on Tinder.
So, back at it tomorrow, huh?
Excited?
Mmm! Oh, yes. You have no idea.
What’s tomorrow?
She’s coming back to work.
Yeah, maternity leave
is officially over.
I feel like I figured out
that I am not cut out
to be a stay-at-home mom.
That’s what I’ve realized.
(chuckles)
Thank you for watching Elijah.
And don’t worry,
he’ll be in day care next week.
Oh, my gosh, don’t be silly.
I’m so excited.
He’s my favorite guy
to hang out with,
right?
(Elijah coos)
I think he looks exactly like
Clara did when she was his age.
Exactly. Don’t you think?
(gasps) Do you?
Are you a pretty boy?
I think he looks
just like his gorgeous daddy.
Right?
(Elijah coos)
You want cake?
Yep, sure. I’m down for cake.
I’ll get it!
Oh, my God! Miller Adams
is following you?
I gave him a ride today.
(Lexie) Oh, got it.
So you were in your car
with him alone
and you didn’t tell me.
Can we talk about it later?
Okay, please.
Why do I know that name?
Miller Adams. Wait.
Is that Hank’s kid?
You remember Hank.
No.
I remember Hank.
There’s still people
named Hank?
He sold drugs
and went to prison.
Someone we know
was Hank’s best customer.
Wait a minute. Hank’s son
is the coolest guy in school?
And it was just
the two of you today?
Miller’s a student of mine.
He’s actually a really good kid.
No offense, but you have him
for 45 minutes a day,
and he’s on his best behavior.
You don’t really know
what kind of kid he is.
We’re not dating anyone
whose father’s a felon.
My God, I just gave him a ride.
Okay, relax.
Nobody’s dating anybody.
Clara is staying away because
the boy has a girlfriend.
(Lexie) I don’t know.
My mom always said
that just because
there’s a goalie
doesn’t mean
you can’t score.
What?
Your mom always says that?
Yeah.(both giggle)
Oh. Thank you. You can just
put those right there.
Okay.
What?
Oh, my God, just say it!
You can’t look at me like that
and not say anything.
My being here bothers you.
Jonah.
Just, I want things
to be okay with us.
(sighs) Okay, should we do this?
Should we just do this now?
Yes! Tell me. Just say it.
Okay.
You graduated and you dumped
Jenny and you disappeared.
You just left. You didn’t
give us any explanation.
Where you were going,
when we would hear
from you next, nothing.
Do you have any idea
how many times I called you?
You didn’t respond once!
I thought we were friends.
We are.
No, no, no. You get my sister pregnant,
move back to town,
and I’m supposed to be,
like, fine with it,
but it’s taking me a minute.
Okay?
That’s fair. And I’m sorry.
But Jenny’s so happy,
and you’ve really
stepped up as a dad.
And I guess
that’s all that matters.
Hey, before I forget.
Happy birthday.
Can’t stay mad at me
forever.
Bye, guys.
Happy birthday.
Bye, Jenny, Jonah.
You’re wobbly.
(Chris) Do not let her drive.
Absolutely not. I got her.
I’m just unlocking the car.
I’ll see you in the morning!
(Jonah) I got it.
Thank you. Happy birthday. (sighs)
(singing)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Aww, I think I might have
sabotaged my own birthday.
What? Why?
I feel like the Hank thing
just threw me off
and I think we might’ve been
too hard on her. Were we?
No! No. We have
to nip that in the bud.
Okay. Yes.
Okay?
Happy birthday.
Aww...
Thank you.
I’ll do the dishes, okay?
I already did them.
(sighs)
Mom.
Yeah?
It’s that time.
Oh, my gosh. Of course it is.Mm-hmm.
And there we go. Yay me!
Big one. Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
(chuckles)
Watermelon’s the best.
Yes, it’s the only flavor
worth the cavities.
I’m proud of how many of these
I’ve checked off.
I know.
"Get a phone.
Any phone is good."
(laughs)
I regret that one.
But you don’t like that one.
I didn’t say anything.
Mmm, you didn’t have to.
It’s just...
the world is so hard.
That world is even harder.
The odds are
stacked against you.
I think it’s smart
if you just--
Yeah, get a degree
in something more...
realistic.
Just as a backup.
But whenever
you were my age,
didn’t you have anything
that you were, like...
actually passionate about?
I went from raising Aunt Jenny
to being pregnant with you
and then raising you and...
I never had time in there
for my passions.
Well, that’s... sad.
I don’t know.
I think...
that your goal this year
should be...
Okay.
"Find your...
passion!"Mm-hmm.
(Morgan) Okay,
I have a question for you.
Mm-hmm...
When you think of me,
what one word comes to mind?
Not something
like "mom" or "wife,"
but something descriptive.
Right now? "Overprotective."
Overprotective?
I didn’t say you were cruel.
I’m exactly as protective
as I’m supposed to be.
Okay, then I’ll pick a new one.
"Predictable."
Predictable?
But not in a bad way.
I prefer overprotective.
I meant, like, dependable.
My soul is dying.
(cell phone dings)
(chuckles)
I love my predictable,
dependable,
overprotective mom.
Well, good.
She’s the only one you’ve got.
Um...
I got to do homework.
Okay.
Love you.
I love you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Okay, I’m taking this.
Good night!
Good night.
(clatters)
(whirring)
Um, no eggs and bacon?
I’m sorry. Did you predict
that I would have
made you breakfast
this morning?
You’re hungry. Um...
Yeah.
Okay.
(Jenny) Knock knock!
Hi.
Knock...
(Morgan) Good catch. Hello.
Hello!
My date for the day!
So, I wrote down his feeding
schedule and sleep schedule.
And he has this bad--
Jenny... you do realize
I’ve raised a human, right?
Two if we count you?
Touché.
Oh. Thanks, honey.
You’re welcome.
Count me out
for dinner tonight. I have a staff meeting.
Okay.
Clara, honey.
Your car is blocking me in.
Hello. Earth to Clara.
(Chris) Car?
Right. Uh-huh...
Bye!
(Morgan) Bye.
(Chris) Bye.
I love you.
(Chris and Clara) Love you!
Okay, man.
There you go.
Yes, oh, yes.
What do you say you skip work,
I skip school,
we go and see a double feature?
I wish. Rain check?
Lame.
Hey...
you okay?
Yeah, just... you know,
school drama. (sighs)
Come here.
Hmm.
You know I’m always here
if you need me.
Yeah. Love you.
Okay? I love you.
I’ll see you tonight.
Sure.Okay.
Hey.
What?
Miller unfollowed me.
Uh, why?
Did you guys get in a fight?
No! We haven’t even spoken
since I dropped him off.
Clara. Honey. I’m blocked in.
Uh, God,
I’m looking for my keys.
Why would he follow me
just to unfollow me
a couple hours later?
I mean...
social media is... confusing?
I don’t know.
Yeah, so are guys.
(car honks)
(Clara chuckles)
(scoffs)
(chuckles)
I love you, Clare Bear.
Mmm, love you.
Mmm... (mumbles)
(both grunting softly)
Bye.
Have fun.
First day back! Whoo!
(chuckles)
("My Fun" playing)
(car honks)
Hey, bitch! (chuckles)
(Clara) Hi.
(Clara grunts)
Thank you.
Mm-hmm. Milady.
Oh, a gift.
Oh, you shouldn’t have. Mm.I know.
♪ You got a good woman ♪
♪ Yeah, babe
You got a good woman ♪
♪ You got a good woman ♪
(Lexie and Clara
continue chattering indistinctly)
♪ Yeah, babe
You got a good woman ♪
♪ You got a good woman ♪
♪ Yeah, babe
You got a good woman ♪
♪ You got a good woman♪
♪ Yeah, babe
You got a good woman ♪
(song ends)
(cell phone buzzes)
(distant chattering)
Oh, shit!
Miller and Shelby
broke up last night.
(scoffs)
Wait. Who told you that?
Emily.
She called her, crying.
Apparently they had a fight
because Miller...
No, no, no. Shelby thought
Miller cheated on her with you.
(laughing) Are you serious?
(chuckles) Yeah. Oh, my God.
Well, I just gave him
a ride home.
Uh-huh. Right.
There are all different
types of rides, Clara.
Ew! Stop it!
(indistinct chattering)
(Lexie) Hey, Uncle Teach.
Good morning.
(Jonah) Hey.
Hey, Mr. Sullivan.
You wanted to talk to me?
Yeah, um... I, uh,
thought you might want to know about this.
It’ll look great for the film
schools you’re applying to.
Lots of talented students
in the drama club could help you out.
Yeah, no, thanks. I just don’t think
film school’s in the cards for me.
You never know.
Keep it, just in case.
Yeah.
(school bell ringing)
(indistinct chatter)
(Clara) You busy?
(Jenny) On my way to lunch.
What’s up?
(Clara) Miller and
his girlfriend broke up.
(Jenny) That’s great!
(Clara) I’m pretty sure he’s
trying to get her back. So...
(Jenny) You don’t want to be
the other girl. Trust me!
(Clara) Wait, you were
the other girl once?
I need to hear about this!
Come on,
I tell you everything.
Hello?
(boy) Watch out!
(all exclaim)
What the--? Oh, my God!
Who threw that? Who threw that?
Who threw that?
You got some
teeth coming, buddy?
Yeah?
That must hurt so much.
(cell phone buzzing)
Oh. My phone’s ringing.
Hello.
Yes, this is she.
What?
(telephone ringing)
Excuse me?
Hi, my name is Morgan Grant.
Um, my husband,
Chris Grant, works here.
They said he was
in a car accident.
(attendant)
Okay. Just have a seat
and I’ll call the doctor
for you.
Is he okay?
Can I talk to him?
(attendant) Let me
get someone to help you. Okay?
(sighs) Okay, could you
try paging my sister?
She works here
in labor and delivery.
Her name is Jenny Davidson.Morgan.
Is he okay? Is Chris okay?
(Jonah) Hi.
Chris? What?
I keep trying to call Jenny,
but she’s not picking up.
Wait,
why are you calling Jenny?
What are you talking about?
Chris was in a car accident.
They told me Jenny
was in a car accident.
Can we get some help?
(woman) I’m working on it.
Please!(Jonah slams desk)
I’m very sorry.
(somber music playing)
(sobbing)
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, thank you, Officer.
(sighs) It was Jenny’s car.
Chris was driving.
Her boss said she wasn’t due
back to work until tomorrow.
That she was still
on maternity leave.
Jesus,
were they having an affair?Don’t.
I-- What else could it be?
No!
I have two funerals to plan.
(tender music playing)
(pastor) "We were buried
with Him by baptism into death.
So that as Christ
was raised from the dead
by the glory of the Father,
we too might walk
into the newness of life."
It is in that new life
that Romans speaks of
that I wish...
I need air.
(pastor) ...for all
who grieve here today.
(sobs softly)
(continues sobbing)
I met Chris
when we were in high school.
Everyone wanted
to be his friend.
His magnetism was...
undeniable.
(footsteps approach)
Hi.
I just couldn’t take it.
It’s...
unbearable.
It’s like she separated
Dad and Aunt Jenny’s funeral
just to torture us all.
(inhales)
I just want to leave. (sighs)
Then let’s leave.
("Mountain" playing)
♪ Losing you is a mountain ♪
♪ Of stillness ♪
(song continues playing)
I feel like getting high.
I’m sure you do.
I’ve never tried it, and I...
really feel like getting
out of my head right now.
Do you have any?
Uh, no. No, I don’t smoke.
But I know how to get some.
Yeah, right. You don’t smoke,
you just have a dealer?
(chuckles)
No, she’s not a dealer.
She’s just my stoner friend.
Hmm.
♪ Play it on over
And over again ♪
Thanks.
♪ Play it on over
And over again ♪
(song ends)
Okay.
Your weed, madam.
Can you light it for me?
Yeah.
I’ve never even smoked
a cigarette before.
(chuckles)
Good. You’ll live longer. Okay, ready?
Yeah.
(coughing)
You okay?
Oh, my God!
Yeah.
Don’t look at me.
(continues coughing)
(laughs)
(chuckling) It’s terrible!
Yeah. Yeah.
I’m so sorry.
Thank you for being here.
Hi.
(sighs) I’m so sorry.
Um, where is Clara?
Oh. I thought
she was with you.
No.
I’m sorry. I don’t--
It’s okay.
I’m not feeling anything.
(laughs)
You are so stoned.
Stop it.
No, I’m kidding. You done?
You’re freaking me out.
I saw your photos on Instagram.
Before the unfollow.
You’re really good.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
You know, now that
you’re single, you can...
always follow me again.
Shelby and I
got back together.
Do you think
I’m into you or something?
Is that why you need to keep informing me
of your relationship status?
Has anyone ever told you
you can be kind of abrasive?
Not in a negative way, but...
No, don’t change the subject.
I mean, if you’re back
with your girlfriend,
why are you here?
I would’ve felt worse
if I didn’t check on you.
Clara Grant!
Oh, my God. Shit!
My mom tracks us all.
Clara Wilma Grant!
(chuckles)
"Wilma?" That can’t be good.
No, full name equals grounded.
Get in the car.
I’ve been calling you!
(thuds)
One second.
Please pretend
this isn’t happening.
Is this better?
Yes!
Get in the car.
Good luck.
(door handle rattling)
Stop staring at him.
Do you have any idea
how worried I was?
Why do we even pay for a phone
if you never answer it?
Sorry.
Oh, great. Thanks for saying "sorry."
Everything’s fine now.
Was that who I think it was?
Look at me! Now!
(gasps)What?
Oh... Were you
smoking pot with him?
What? No!
And his name is Miller,
and no, we were just talking.
You skipped your father’s
funeral to get high?
Well, I stayed for most of it.
It was
your father’s funeral.
Okay, and we should have
just had one funeral for the both of them!
How long am I grounded for?
Forever. Like...
(exhales)
(blows)
We should really
toast to burning in hell.
Yeah! To...
Outer Darkness.
To Outer Darkness!
Outer Darkness is
the lowest degree of heaven...
(knock on door)
...in the Mormon faith.
You have the Celestial Degree,
which is--
(knock on door)
Hello.Hey.
Come in.
Okay.
I, uh... I tried calling.
Just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
Aw, that’s nice of you.
(sighs) I’m so good.
Where’s Elijah?
Uh, my mom’s got him.
You’re sleeping
on the couch?
Yes, I am.
I’m also drinking wine.
Would you like to join me?
I’m okay.
Look, we need to talk.
Mmm...
Nah, I’m good.
Don’t you want to know
why they lied?
No.
Why they were together?
Why Chris
was driving her car?
Jonah... (shushes)
(softly)
Clara could hear you.
And where is Chris’s car,
by the way?
(breath shudders)
Do you want that drink now?
(sighs)
(car doors opening and closing)
(engine starts)
(sighs)
(car departing)
(Morgan) Oh, my God.
There’s his car.
You stay here, I’ll go.
Popcorn still hot?
Clara?
(scoffs) I thought for sure
you’d be grounded.
Yeah. No, I am. But I escaped.
(shushes)
(chuckles) Theater 4 has
about 30 minutes left. Um...
What’s playing?
Oh, the latest
Mission: Impossible. You know...
Tom Cruise saves the world
by running fast.
(chuckles) Great.
Perfect, I’ll take it.
No, no, family gets in free.
So if anyone asks,
you’re my sister.
Right. (chuckles)
Um, I think I’d almost
rather pay than pretend we’re siblings.
(chuckles)
Uh, you got, um...
Theater 4.
Right. Thanks.
(sighs)
Don’t start.
(car door opens)
(sighs)
He used to bring me here.
On getaways.
I’m sorry.
They never checked out
and left all their shit.
(sighs)
I gave this to Jenny
last Christmas.
Morgan, wait.
Wait, where are you going?
Morgan!
(Morgan) Asshole.
(Jonah) Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Morgan.
(grunting loudly)
(thudding)
(screaming)
I did everything for them!
(car alarm blaring)
(grunting)
Fuck!
(continues grunting loudly)
(screams)
Didn’t know this movie
was a tearjerker.
Yeah, uh...
my dad loved movies.
We used to come here a lot.
That’s why I was crying.
You know, um...
Refuge Coffee plays, like,
old horror movies once a month.
So, you know, if you want to...
I should probably get going.
I’m sorry,
did I say something wrong?
No, um, just...
smiling feels wrong right now.
(sniffles)
But I’ll see you at school.
Yeah.
Thank you.
How are you so calm?
Trust me, I’m not, but...
I don’t know...
they cut you deeper than me.
Clara can never know.
She’s been
through enough already. Just promise me.
She worshipped them.
It would absolutely
destroy her.
Yeah, okay.
(engine starts)
(sighs)
(thuds)
Argh! Goddamn it!
(grunts)
(crunches)
Ugh! (strains)
(Clara) What the hell?
(Morgan) Damn it!
Mom? Oh, my God.
Mom, are you okay?
What part of "grounded"
did you not understand?
I’m sorry. You just left,
and I didn’t want to be alone.
(sighs) Come on.
What is happening? Dad’s car?
I am tired, Clara.
I don’t want to talk about this.
Who would do that?
Did you call the cops?
It’s trashed!
You are grounded!
Just go to your room!
Be in your room!
What, I’m grounded
from the kitchen now?
Yes!
Ugh! (grunts)
(panting)
(Miller) You get home okay?
Just checking on you.
(Clara) Thanks for
cheering me up tonight.
You’re the best sibling
I never had.
(knocking on door)
(loud knocking on door)
Jesus.
Jonah, what’s going on?
It’s the middle of the night.
I can’t do this.
(Morgan) Is he okay?
He’s fine, I’m not.
Hey, what’s going on?What?
Hi, bubba.
Do you mind
taking him for a second?
I’m just gonna
talk to Jonah. Yeah.
Hi, silly!
And here, take this. Jonah!
What the hell
is going on with you?
When he smiled tonight...
What? What happened?
He has Chris’s fucking smile.
(Clara) Everything okay?
(car door opening and closing)
Uh, yes! Yes, honey!
Um, Jonah’s
just not feeling well.
But do you mind feeding Elijah?
I think he’s hungry.
Check if there’s
a bottle in the bag.
Sure.
Thank you.
So what is your plan?
I don’t know.
I need to clear my head.
Oh, okay. Uh, when
will you be back?
I don’t know.
Okay, I see.
So you’re leaving again.
You’re just gonna
dump your son on me
and then you’re just gonna
come back who knows when?
Not my son.
("How’s It Going to Be"
playing)
♪ I’m only pretty sure ♪
♪ That I can’t take any more ♪
♪ Before you take a swing ♪
♪ I wonder
What are we fighting for? ♪
♪ When I say out loud
"I wanna get out of this" ♪
♪ I wonder, is there anything
I’m gonna miss? ♪
(Morgan) Don’t judge me.
Receipts! Proof! Time line!
Screenshots!
(bleep) ...everything to prove
that you are a(bleep) bully
and a(bleep) troll...
(song fades)
Oh, hey, honey.
(indistinct chattering over TV)
Hmm...
Okay.
You’ve been in the same
clothes for days.
Mm-hmm...
You are camped out
on the couch.
Oh, sorry.
And you’re drinking,
which you never do.
And you’re taking care
of somebody else’s kid?
(Morgan) That reminds me.
Can you go to the store
and pick up some formula?
I went and I got everything
but formula,
and we’ve just ran out.
No, no, no. Tell Jonah to do it.
It’s his responsibility.
Clara, his whole world
just got turned upside-down.
Our world just got
turned upside-down.
Well, I can’t go.
Can you go?
Can you go? I love you.
It’s the one
with the green label.
(knocking on door)
(indistinct chattering over TV)
Jonah, it’s been two days!
Dude, I know you’re in there!
I can hear the TV.
(doorbell ringing)
(knocking on door continues)
Okay!
(sighs)
Geez.
If the school board
ever saw this,
you’d totally
be out of a job.
Not that you care.
Dude, what are you doing?
Cleaning.
No, I mean
what are you doing?
Why is my mom
taking care of your kid?
(sighs)
You wouldn’t understand.
(chuckles) I love whenever
adults who are behaving
like children
say that to children
who are behaving like adults.
Clever.
Getting rid of Jenny’s stuff?
(sighs) She never really
got around to unpacking.
You know how she was.
Aren’t you even, like,
the tiniest bit worried
about Elijah?
Of course. I’m just...
I’m not in a good place, okay?
Yeah, and neither is my mom.
She just lost her husband
and her sister.
Yeah, and I just lost
my best friend
and the mother of my son.
And I just lost
my dad and my aunt.
Thanks. Now we’ve established
we’re all broken
and totally messed up.
You know what?
Elijah rolled over last night.
What, he did?
No, but he’s going to. Soon.
And you’re gonna miss it.
You’re gonna miss
all of these memories
that you’re
never gonna get back.
So...
how about you go
and get your son?
Hello? How about you go
and get your son? (sighs)
(softly) Yeah.
Um, also, I’ll clean your house
for 50 bucks.
Yeah, okay.
And...
on the way back,
get baby formula.
The one with the green label.
Got it. Thanks, Clara.
Hmm...
(babbles) Are you hungry?
Oh, perfect timing!
He is so hungry
and ready to eat.
Hey, can I?
(voice breaking)
I’m here, buddy. Daddy’s here.
(sobbing)
I’ll never leave you again.
How I love you.
(Elijah squeals)
I know, I know.
I’m mad at me, too, bud.
I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry.
(sniffles)
(sobs softly)
(door closes)
Um, hi.
I sent you three minutes up the road
to get formula.
Where have you been?
Where’s Elijah?
Jonah came to pick him up.
What? That’s crazy.
Looks like
we don’t need formula.
Yeah, also crazy, you still
haven’t told me where you were.
Oh, my God. I am here now.
Why does it matter?
You were with Miller,
weren’t you?
Geez, Mom.
It’s like you always do this.
You have to control my life
because you don’t have one.
Can I go now?
No!
’Cause you still haven’t
told me where you were!
I was cleaning
Jonah’s house.
Yeah, right.
Solving your problems.
Why do you always
assume the worst of me?
(door closes)
(cell phone dings)
(Miller) Where you at?
(Clara) Refuge.
(Miller) On my way.
Stalk much?
It’s not my fault you’re not
aware of your surroundings.
Look.
I don’t know how I feel
about being your backup plan
every time things go south
with your girlfriend.
I don’t have a girlfriend.
I broke up with her.
For good.
You want to go for a ride?
Just smile and act natural.
(Clara) Why do I always
get roped into this?
The things we do for love.
Of... pizza.
(Clara chuckling)
He’s gonna take
your whole hand off.
I know.
How’s he doing?
Cancer.
I’m so sorry, Miller.
Yeah.
He’s kind of like
the only parent I ever had.
My mom died when I
was young and my dad...
Well, whatever.
Kind of makes it hard
to think about college.
You know, because I don’t know
who’s gonna look after him.
I think you are.
When we drive home together
on the weekends.
It’s like a two-hour drive.
Yeah, but I don’t even know
if I’m gonna get in, so...
Only one way to find out.
I should’ve gotten rid
of that door years ago.
Why didn’t you?
Well, it’s Chris’s
childhood home.
"Don’t change a thing."
But...
here we are, 17 years later.
You know, I remember
in school seeing you draw rooms and houses
in the margins
of your papers.
You were really good.
You were spying on me?
(chuckles) I sat behind you.
Class was boring.
You weren’t.
Oh, you must be thinking
of someone else.
Trust me, I was never
thinking of anyone else.
(clears throat)
Clara should be home.
(sighs)
I am so late.
Okay, before you go,
I have to tell you something.
When you said
you were my backup plan, I wanted to laugh,
because...
if anything, Shelby
was my backup plan to you.
(scoffs)
What do you mean?
Look, the reason I broke up
with Shelby is because,
when I went to sleep at night,
I wasn’t thinking about her.
And when I woke up,
I wasn’t thinking
about her either, Clara.
I was thinking about you.
And I hated the way
that made me feel.
It made me feel like
I was cheating, or something.
And I’m not that kind of guy.
I’ve had a thing for you
for a very long time, too.
Okay, who’s the stalker now?
("Chesapeake" playing)
♪ I can’t hardly wait ♪
That’s not how I thought
our first kiss would be like.
(song continues playing)
Like what?
Sweet.
How did you think
it would be?
♪ I was all covered in sound ♪
Like this.
♪ When you asked me
To turn it down ♪
♪ Didn’t even think
It was loud ♪
♪ Can you hear it now? ♪
(cell phone buzzing)
Hi, it’s Clara.
Leave a message.
Nothing.
(phone line beeps)
Oh, she’s totally
screening my calls.
I should, uh... I should
probably go pick up Elijah.
How is he?
Good. Yeah.
My mom’s been a huge help.
Does she, um...
Does she know?
No, I didn’t tell her.
Look, I know you don’t think
it’s a good idea
to tell Clara, but...
if she and Elijah
are half-siblings...
Oh, my God.
Just hearing you say that is...
When he’s older,
he might want to know.
And I think she might, too.
Yeah, maybe. I don’t know.
I never know these days
what she wants.
I mean, she probably
doesn’t, either.
You remember that age.
Everything felt so intense,
complicated. (chuckles)
I...
I can’t really remember
what it felt like.
You know what gets me there
is the music of the time.
You hear a song
and it just wrecks you.
Takes you right back.
Okay...
try me.
(sighs)
("Dakota" playing
over cell phone)
What is this one again?
You really don’t remember?
("Dakota" continues playing
over speakers)
(gasps) Hey!
Hey, careful!
If you ruin this and I don’t
get into State, I am suing you.
It’s the weekend. Come swim!
(laughing) Come on.
I’m just gonna
keep splashing you
if you don’t come in.
No, you’re not.
All right. Here we go.
No!
(chuckles)
(Morgan) Okay.
That’s not bad.
It’s perfect.
(Morgan) Ooh...
Okay, are you satisfied?
Definitely. (chuckles)
Ooh.
♪ Made me feel
Like the one ♪
Ooh.
♪ The one ♪
♪ You made me feel
Like the one ♪
♪ Made me feel
I’m worried we got it wrong.
♪ The one ♪
(Jenny) Hey, look what
we got at the garage!
(Chris) Yo! What up?
That’s right.
Yeah, we have a party!
♪ Drinking with you ♪
♪ When drinking was new ♪
("Dakota" continues playing
over cell phone)
(Clara) Hey, I’m sorry.
I... I know that I’m late
and I’m grounded.
Um...
(song stops)
Um... My phone was off
and I was distracted. I’m...
sorry.
Hi.
(softly) Hey.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah,
you’re very grounded.
Just go to your room, I guess.
That’s it?
(Morgan) Mmm...
No, it’s fine. Yeah. Okay.
I swear, I have no idea
what’s going on with my mom lately.
Yeah, give her time.
She’s dealing with a lot.
(Lexie) Whoa, hey!
Find a boyfriend for me yet?
Actually, yeah. Um...
You know Efren?
(Lexie) The AV nerd?
Yo, Efren!
(Efren) Ow! Oh...
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh...
Uh, come here, man.
(grunts)
(softly) Okay, hey.
He’s really nice.
(Lexie) Don’t tell him
to come over here.
No, you’ll love him.
What’s up, dude?
(sighs)
Hi, Efren.
(Efren) Hi, Clara.
What’s up, dude?
What’s up?
Do you know Lexie?
Uh, not really.
No. No offense, though!
It’s just that, um...
you always seemed
kind of scary.
I am scary.
Yeah, uh... (clears throat)
Do you have any tattoos?
(scoffing)
Hell, no! No! What?
Wait, why? Should I?
Don’t you have to be, like, 18?
(mumbles, chuckles awkwardly)
I don’t want
to do that, so, uh...
(knocking on door)
Hey.
Something’s wrong.
He feels really hot...
(Elijah fussing)
...and he’s not acting
like himself.
Okay, let’s see. Oh, bubba.
Oh, yeah, looks like
he’s got a little bug.
Feel the back of his neck.
Yeah. Buddy.Yeah.
Oh, we’re gonna take
care of you. Come here.
Okay.
Uh, acetaminophen
always helps.
It does.
But firsts are the worst.
First fall. First fever.
(Elijah fussing)
First tooth.
Oh. This is a cold.
God, how am I gonna
do this, buddy?
Oh, you just will.
Hey. Is Elijah all right?
Yeah, it’s just a cold.
Yeah, I’m still new at this.
Your mom’s helping me out.
Where are you going?
Um, to the movies with Lexie.
Oh, weird.
I didn’t realize Miller had
changed his name to Lexie.
Doesn’t he have
a girlfriend?
They broke up.
Oh, okay.
And 30 seconds later,
he’s with you.
Mom.
I’m just saying.
He’s not the kind of guy that’s worth
throwing your life away for, Clara.
(scoffing)
Throwing my life away?
Jesus, Mom,
I’m going to the movies.
(sighs)
Don’t look at me.
I’m Team Miller. (chuckles)
Sorry.
I am putting you
to work for that.
That’s fair.
Right?
Should we put Dada to work?
(Jonah) Ugh! Got it.
So, I think we can
just take this entire thing
down in one piece.
I just have to empty it.
(chair sliding)
I’m so excited!
(sighs)
Morgan.
This is Jenny’s handwriting.
Right under our noses?
I don’t need to read them.
Oh, come on. You’re not even
a little bit curious?
It’s in the past.
Huh... Must be nice.
You are not the one
living in his house.
Living in his parents’ house.
Surrounded by his things.
His stuff is everywhere!
It is everywhere!
That painting!
That horrible painting.
Jenny took me
to a specific place
to buy that painting
for Chris’s birthday,
and I was, like, "Chris?
A painting for his birthday?
Why are we doing this?"
And she was, like,
"You don’t know him like I do."
I thought she was kidding.
She wasn’t kidding.
All right. I have an idea.
Oh, my God,
I hate this thing.
I’m so excited. I’m doing this.
Go. Go. Go!
It’s gonna be messy.
Yes.
But it’s fine.
We don’t care.
Look at how ugly that thing is.
Ugh! Okay.
(groans)
Ugh! This painting!
Give it a little crow hop!
Oh, my God! (exclaims)
(grunting)
Don’t drag it.
Oh, there we go.
(Jonah grunts)
Okay.
(chuckles)
Where are we going?
Patience, Grasshopper.
Okay.
Oh...
What is all this?
I’m wooing you with
my popcorn-making skills.
Really? (chuckles)
Oh...
Perfect combination
of butter and salt.
Hmm... Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh. Yup.
Where is everyone?
Oh, they’re
cleaning the floors.
But it takes
48 hours for it to dry,
so we have the theater
to ourselves.
What are we watching?
It’s a surprise.
Oh.
(chuckles)
My bad. (chuckles)
You ready, Efren?
(Efren) It’s coming right up!
Hi, Clara.
Hi, Efren.
Thank you.
(mellow music playing
over theater speakers)
I cannot get over
how much of a mess this is.
(chuckles)
It’s insane.
I just realized I got some
on the ceiling. (chuckles)
(Morgan laughing)
It’s everywhere.
Oh, wait, wait. Look at me.
I got you.
What is it? Oh, my God.
What do you think it is?
(both laughing)
How?
(continues laughing)
That’s insane!
It’s nice hearing you laugh.
You, too, Mr. Serious.
What?
Oh, come on. Jonah.
In school,
you were always so serious.
You were also mysterious.
With the glasses?
I mean, come on.
But I kind of made it a point
to notice everything about you.
Like what?
Um, I don’t know,
like your insane hatred
for watermelon Jolly Ranchers.
Weirdo.
They’re the best.
I didn’t hate them.
I actually love them.
I just saved them for you
because I know
they’re your favorite.
(Elijah cooing)
Gonna check on Elijah.
Morgan.
Jonah.
We’re both going through
a lot right now...
No, don’t do that.
And we’re feeling very
vulnerable and we are angry.
That’s not what this is.
I’ve wanted you since the day I met you.
(sighs)
My biggest regret is
not telling you how I felt
before Chris swooped in.
I should have fought
harder for you.
And I think
you felt the same.
Yeah, but...
it doesn’t matter.
(choked up) It doesn’t matter
what I felt then,
it doesn’t matter
what I feel now.
This is my life now.
Clara’s my world, that’s it.
This isn’t about Clara.
Everything is about Clara.
And protecting her
from the truth?
Yes.
And as a matter of fact,
take these with you.
I don’t want her
to find them, okay?
You’ll get there, but you
do not know what it is like
to put somebody else
before yourself.
I’ve been doing that
for 17 years.
I do know what it’s like.
Okay? That’s why I left
all those years ago.
It’s because I had respect
for them. For you.
Leaving
was the hardest thing I have ever done.
Okay?
I left because I loved you.
I still love you.
What about Jenny?
Did you love her or...?
I did.
And I wanted
to do right by her.
But she didn’t
do right by me.
And neither did
my best friend.
But I’m not gonna
let their betrayal
dictate the rest of my life
and you shouldn’t, either...
(Elijah cooing, fussing)
Cher, get in here.
What’s up, Daddy?
What the hell is that?
A dress.
Says who?
Calvin Klein.
It looks like underwear.
Go upstairs
and put something over it.
Just so you know,
I am a virgin.
I know a cure for that.
(chuckles)
No, I’m glad you told me.
And just so you’re aware,
I’m in no hurry.
I’m having a wonderful time
not having sex with you.
(chuckles) Okay.
Good.
Because I think that
we should wait to have sex
until prom night.
Cheesy? Sure,
but what do you say?
I mean,
shouldn’t I ask you first?
Yeah, sure,
but no lame promposals.
Well, yeah,
I hate those things anyway.
("This Far South" playing)
("This Far South"
continues playing)
♪ You remind me ♪
♪ Of every single
Dogwood tree ♪
♪ When I tried to reach out ♪
♪ I never see you
This far south no more ♪
(Lexie) There we go.
Is this gonna wash off?
Is this--
Wait, are you getting it?
Yeah, I’m getting it all.
(Efren) No, don’t do that.
(chuckles)
Oh, my gosh, he’s so cute!
♪ Any less than all of me ♪
♪ But that won’t work out ♪
(whirring)
♪ If words can’t fall
Out my mouth no more ♪
♪ Angel ♪
(clacks)
(exclaims)
♪ Walk me ♪
Through your garden ♪
(loud thud, shattering)
(exclaims)
♪ Won’t you please again? ♪
(sighs)
Get me the hell out of here.
♪ The nerves
Inside my heart ♪
♪ In Germantown tonight ♪
♪ I’m learning ♪
♪ That it’s not good to fly ♪
(indistinct chatter)
♪ I’ve chosen ♪
♪ The habit
That I’m dropping ♪
(song continues playing)
(crashes)
(screams)
(exclaims)
(laughing)
No, no, no, you have to
watch this part.
(indistinct chattering
over speakers)
Oh, wow, that’s--
Yeah, that’s a lot.
(laughing)
Oh, my God.
♪ If sand could rise
When we grow old ♪
Okay, what are we playing for?
Cigarettes.
Mmm...
I don’t smoke. Money?
I don’t have any.
Mmm...
Let’s play for air.
Stop trying
to make air happen, Gramps.
(song continues playing)
(scoffs)
♪ Angel, walk me ♪
♪ Through your garden
And your trees ♪
♪ But please don’t
Reach out ♪
♪ ’Cause I won’t be
This far south again ♪
♪ The nerves
Inside my heart ♪
♪ In Germantown tonight ♪
♪ I’m learning
That it’s not good to fly ♪
♪ I’ve chosen the habit ♪
♪ That I’m dropping ♪
♪ Coming down’s exhausting ♪
♪ I think
I deserve some rest ♪
(song ends)
Did I do something wrong?
Um...
No, actually the opposite.
(both laughing)
Sorry.
Don’t be sorry.
(sighs) But, um...
I do have to get to work.
Dread.
Time for me to go home.
Things still bad?
Yeah, my mom’s on some kick
redoing every room
in the house right now.
She donated their bed.
All my dad’s clothes.
I mean,
it’s like she’s, like...
trying to make it
like he never even existed.
And this’ll be
my first birthday without him.
Wait, when?
Tomorrow.
What? It’s not a big deal.
It is to me.
Happy birthday.
(chuckles)
(knocking on door)
Hey.
Uh...
Morgan... (sighs)
I didn’t mean for what I said
to make you--
Oh, my God. I can’t believe
I just did that. I...
(chuckles) I didn’t know
I was gonna do that.
I had a whole speech
planned.
Now I just--
(exclaims)
Oh, my God.
Clara? Clara?
(knocking) Open your door
so I can talk to you, please.
Go away! You’re disgusting!
Clara. Clara,
open the door, please.
(crying)
Clara, come on.
Please open your door
and let me talk to you.
(panting)
(knocking)
Clara?
Jonah, just go.
(tender music playing)
(Clara) Come over after work.
(Miller) To your house?
(Clara) Yes. First window
left of the front door.
Bring a condom.
(Miller) Are you sure?
What are you doing, Clara?
(wood clacking)
(thuds)
(Clara) Oh!
What about your mom?
She’s asleep.
You look beautiful.
(chuckles)
I just wasn’t expecting this
this soon, you know.
We said prom.
Well, at midnight
it’s my birthday.
And I don’t want
to wait anymore.
Are you sure?
I’m sure.
You’re gonna have to--
I can’t get it. (chuckles)
Clara...
I love you.
I love you, too.
(gasps softly)
(breathing heavily)
You okay?
(Clara) Yeah.
Are you okay?
Why are you crying?
Did I do something wrong?
No, no, no.
You’re fine, it’s not you.
No, talk to me. What is it?
I...
I’m sorry.
(groans) It’s just...
God, my...
mom and Jonah...
I just saw them kissing.
And my dad
and Aunt Jenny are dead,
and they’re making out?
I just don’t know how long
it’s been going on
or what’s happening, and I’m...
really confused
and I’m just so angry.
I’m just really angry.
And that’s why
you called me over here?
(breathing heavily)
Because you’re mad
at your mom? Miller, no, I--
No, I-- Wait.
Where are you going?
You weren’t ready.
We said prom, and you
want to get back at them.
I promise, it...
I’m sorry. It wasn’t personal.
Exactly.
The one thing that should’ve
been most personal
wasn’t personal at all.
Look, I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, okay?
I... Please, just stay.
(sobbing)
I’ll stay
till you fall asleep.
I’m sorry.
(birds chirping)
(Morgan) Clara.
(gasps)
(both exclaim)
Oh, my God!
What the hell, Clara?
(Clara) Mom...
(Morgan) What is happening?
You need to leave right now!Yeah.
Out the door like a person!
What the hell?
Yeah, um...
Clara, I’ll see you at school.
Okay.
No, he won’t see you at school.
Yes, he will.
What, are you grounding me from school now?
Uh, yeah, I’m grounding you
from school.
You’re 16 years old,
I can ground you
from wherever
I want to ground you from!
Actually, Mother, I’m 17.
But I guess you were too busy with Jonah
to remember that it’s my birthday.
Oh, no, I remembered.
How could I forget that?
And we are having your
birthday dinner here tonight.
I don’t want it.
You will be here whether
you hate my guts or not!
(clamoring)
(Clara) Hey.
(cell phone dings)
(Miller) Hey. You okay?
(Clara) I don’t know.
Are we okay?
(dings)
(Miller) Don’t worry.
It’s your birthday.
(clacks)
(exclaims) Oh, my God! Jerk.
Still not aware
of your surroundings?
Stop.
(chuckles)
When did you have time?
Uh, right before school.
I, um...
I didn’t really know
what you wanted, so I, uh...
Ta-da!
It’s perfect.
I love it.
Um...
Birthday dinner.
Tonight at my place.
That sounds
like a terrible idea.
It’s my birthday.
I can invite whoever I want.
Please?
Um...Hey, Miller.
Can you give us a minute?
Yeah, um...
I’ll see you tonight,
Clara.
I have nothing to say to you.
It’s like neither of you
ever cared about them.
Clara, it’s complicated.
Let me guess.
I wouldn’t understand?
No, it’s just...
(sighs) It’s not my place.
That’s for you
and your mom to discuss.
Yeah, well, I never want
to talk to her again.
Look, I know you’re pissed.
But the last thing she’d
ever want is to hurt you.
You know that.
I’m gonna be late for class.
Well, it’s my class,
and we’re both late!
(school bell rings)
Clara.
(car beeps)
(door opens)
(sighs)
Hi. I don’t know if we’ve
been properly introduced.
Oh. Sure we have.
You’re Miller Adams.
You’re the boy
that kidnapped my daughter
from her father’s funeral
to get her high
and then you climbed into her bedroom
window last night to have sex with her.
Was that not you?
That was you.
Yeah, I think I’m just gonna--
It’s my birthday.
I can invite whoever I want.
(Clara scoffs)
I can see
you’ve done the same.
(Jonah) Oh, no, I just
came to drop this off.
I won’t stay.
(Clara) No!
Stay. Join us.
Yeah. Stay.
This’ll be fun! (chuckles)
(fork and china
clinking loudly)
(Morgan clears throat)
No.
(fork and china
continue clinking)
Awkward!
(chuckles nervously)
This is really good,
Mrs. Grant. Thank you.
Thank you, Miller.
And thank you, Mr. Sullivan,
for the recommendation letter.
It means... It means a lot.
Of course. Yeah.
You finish your short film?
No, we’ve been
too busy having sex. (spits)
It’s a joke.
Party! Lighten up, people.
(fork and china
continue clinking)
Oh, I really like
the changes that you’ve made
around the place,
Mrs. Grant.
Thank you, Lexie.
Bit by bit.
Yeah, Mom’s good with a tool.
Clara!
Morgan!
Oh... (sighs)
How about cake?
As you both know, my mom
makes the best cakes ever.
Though, this year you must’ve
gotten it done really fast
because this morning you didn’t
even remember it was my birthday.
No, I remembered.
The weirdest thing
happened, though.
Something about seeing
you and Miller asleep in bed together
just kind of knocked me
off my game a little bit.
We didn’t sleep.
(stutters) Yes, we did.
Clara.I know.
It’s inappropriate. Stop.
(scoffs) Speaking
of not appropriate,
how long have you been boning
your dead friend’s wife?
(sighs)
Clara...
(glass clinks)
A toast.
To my mother.
This year, she has gone
from the most predictable
housewife ever
to starring in her own
"Real Housewife" show.
Drama and scandal
at every turn.
As for me, I will be
skipping season two,
because I got accepted
into UNCSA’s drama program.
What?
Yay!
Cheers to me.
Okay, I can’t do this.
Thank you, Mrs. Grant.
Thank you, Mr. Sullivan.
Enjoy dinner.
Miller?
Clara?
(sighs)
Lexie, I think you should
head home right about now.
I’m staying over,
remember?
We’ve all got to ride
this shit out together.
Miller, hey, wait! Hey!
When were you gonna
tell me you got in?
(voice breaks)
I only found out today.
Congratulations.
I’m on the wait list.
Shit. Miller.
No!
You keep using me
to piss your mom off, and I’m done with it.
Hey, hey, you’re done?
Okay, so what, you’re just gonna sleep
with me last night and then dump me?
No, you don’t get
to throw that in my face.
I was the one taken advantage
of last night, not you.
I’m sorry. I screwed up.
I mean, they disrespected
the two most important
people in my life,
and I’m supposed to
sit here and pretend like I’m fine with it?
When are you gonna realize
you’re not the only one with problems?
Okay, Gramps
starts chemo next week,
and you’re gonna go off
to some amazing school,
and I’m gonna be stuck here
in Nowheresville.
(engine starts)
(sobs)
God.
(sniffles)
Hey.
So it seems like now
is the perfect time...
(bottles clink)
...to give you
your birthday present.
(chuckles)
Let’s get out of here.
(sniffles)
What? Wait.
Where are we going?
I want to see my dad
and Aunt Jenny.
(engine starts)
Did they really just take off?
(owl hooting)
I miss you, Aunt Jenny.
We miss you so much.
Mmm...
Oh.
You were like my best friend.
It was...
Go ahead.
No, you know what I mean.
Yeah. No, I get it.
She was cool as shit.
Mmm...
Pour one out for the--
Yeah.
Yeah. Drink up, girl.
Good call.
She liked this stuff.
Yeah. I do, too.
Mmm...
Let’s, um...
Let’s go see my dad.
Yeah, lead the way.
(both chattering indistinctly)
(yawning) Can you believe
I am dating Efren?
Can you believe I lost
my virginity to Miller?
(snickers) No.
Wait. And like what,
are you guys broken up now?
(sighs) I don’t even know.
Hmm...
I mean,
I’d break up with me.
I mean, it’s, like...
(voice cracks)
I don’t know.
Part of me
did it to hurt her, and then I just...
ended up hurting him.
Like a walking disaster.
(crying)
All of this is my fault.
(sobbing) I’m so sorry, Dad.
(Lexie grunts softly)
(Morgan) Clara?
We need to talk.
(retches)
Bye, car.
(toilet flushing)
I’m never drinking again.
It’s all my fault.
Aww... You got angry
at your mom and you got drunk.
It happens to almost
every teenager in the world.
The accident.
It was my fault.
What?
(sighs) My head.
Yeah, that’s gonna hurt. A lot.
Here, sit down. Take this.
Last night you said something,
and I wanted
to ask you about it.
Might have been
the wine talking, but...
you said you...
blame yourself
for the accident?
Why would you think that?
I don’t...
know. (sobs)
(sobbing)
I mean, it’s my fault that they’re dead.
What?
I mean, I didn’t know
that she was driving.
And I was just...
text bombing Jenny,
and now they’re...
Oh, my God, sweetheart, sweetheart,
she was not driving.
Your dad was driving.
It is so not your fault.
It is not your fault.
What aren’t you telling me?
Why were they
really together?
I didn’t want to tell you this,
because...
I would never want you
to think less of them.
But your father
and Aunt Jenny, they were...
Having an affair?
For how long?
A long time, apparently.
But you didn’t think
to tell me that?
I was trying to protect
your memories of them
because your dad made some
really big mistakes, yes,
but he also did a lot right.
And the same goes
for Aunt Jenny.
And they loved you so much.
You and Jonah, I saw you.
That was the first time
we have ever kissed, I swear.
I would never have done that
to your father
or Aunt Jenny,
especially to you. Never.
But they did it to you.
Yeah.
Do you regret marrying him?
Oh, no, no, I don’t.
I couldn’t.
I would go back and do it all
the exact same way if I could.
Because if even one thing
happened differently,
you wouldn’t be here,
and you are the best thing
in my life for miles.
Clara, there is no life that
I want that you are not in.
(sniffles)
(cell phone buzzes)
You deserve to be happy.
No regrets, right?
We both deserve
to be happy, okay?
(Lexie) Oh, my God,
what time is it?
Oh, Clara, we’re gonna
be late for school.
(Morgan and Clara)
It’s the weekend!
Oh...
(chuckles) Lexie.
(Clara) I’m sorry.
I was wrong about everything.
There’s so much
I need to tell you.
Lame, Clara.
(cell phone chimes)
(Miller) I’m sorry, too.
How soon can I see you?
How can I help you?
(man)
Can I get some Gummy Bears?
Yeah.Efren.
We--
Efren!
Um, sorry.
Where is he?
He’s... He’s...
Movie about to start, man.
Hey, Miller, I’ve got Clara here,
and she’s headed your way.
No, she’s running.
She’s sprinting.
Excuse me.
(indistinct chattering)
(laughing)
(thunder rumbling)
(rain pattering)
Always miss one.
("Splits Are Parted"
playing)
We did get it wrong.
It should have been us.
I love you.
♪ Splits are parted
Since we parted in April ♪
♪ Go to bed now
Sing me a song ♪
♪ Gonna see me going inside ♪
♪ Gonna see me
Going inside ♪
(song continues playing)
(chuckling) Thank you.
♪ Oh, I could love you ♪
♪ Oh, then it’d be easy ♪
♪ Oh, I’ll come find you ♪
(song ends)
(Clara) Yeah. No. Sure.
(cell phone ringing)
Thank you.
Hi, Mom.
(Morgan) Almost done?
Yeah, I’m just wrapping up.
(Morgan) Great.
Want to watch a movie tonight?
Mm-hmm. I’m on my way.
(Morgan) See you soon,
Clare Bear.
(Lexie) I think
it’s more than enough.
We’re filling two whole bowls.
That’s a whole bag of popcorn.
(Morgan) Are you sure?
(Lexie) Yeah, absolutely.
I’m back.
Oh, hello.
Hi.
What’s going on?
(Lexie) A surprise, bitch!
Lexie.
(Lexie) Sorry.
Hello.
(Lexie) Come with me.Where?
Oh... (laughing)
Close your eyes.
Okay, just be careful, honey.
What is happening?
Is this necessary?
Yes!
I’m gonna switch my hand. Okay.
(continues laughing) Hello?
And... Okay, stop!
Or else you’re gonna fall off.
And... Ta-da!
(chuckles)
What is this?
Oh, nothing.
(Lexie giggles)
Miller?
(Morgan) We did it.
We pulled it off.
What are you doing?
Humor me. Grab a seat.
Grab some popcorn! (Clara chuckles)
Hello.
I know, right?
He’s starting.
Is it starting?
(Miller) Yeah.
Is this fine? Yeah, okay.
(indistinct chattering)
Squeeze.
Okay.
(Efren) Yeah, okay.
(Miller) Okay, I want
to start off with saying,
thank you, everyone,
for being here tonight. Um...
As we all know, I was on
the wait list for film school.
And, um...
I got in.
(all cheering)
(Gramps) Attaboy!
I’ll be darned. Good for you.
But I’m going to defer and
stick around here for a while
and take care of my gramps
the next couple rounds of chemo.
That’s a bunch of horseshit.
Boy, I’ve been telling you
since you were a little fart
you could have my air.
My air rights.
I bought them
when your gram and me
lived in New York,
back in the day.
What are you talking about?
Well, in big cities,
you can buy the rights to air.
So that, you know,
people can’t build
in front of your building
or on top of you.
And I’ve owned a little piece
in Union Square worth about...
I don’t know,
half a million dollars
last time I checked.
(gasps)
But the point is we got
enough money to afford
any home health care
if necessary and your tuition.
(chuckles)
Uh, this is...
amazing news
that we’ll talk about later.
Sorry. My bad.
(Morgan laughs)
But tonight
is about you, Clara.
And this movie is for you.
And naturally, you’re the star.
Efren, hit it.
(Morgan gasps)
(Gramps chuckles)
It’s been 14 years, Mama.
I’m dead.
You’re a grandmother, Mama.
Don’t you remember?
(Miller over speakers) Hey,
Efren, take the camera from me.
(Efren over speakers)
Yeah, got it, got it.
I directed this part. This...
Shut up. She’s acting.
Okay. Sorry. Sorry.
Look at my grandson.
I think he’s in love.
(thuds)
(chuckles)
(Clara) Let us
look at one another.
What’s her name?
(Clara) I can’t go on.
I never realized...
Uh, Clara.
Clara Grant.
Take me back.
Up the hill to my grave.
Oh, earth,
you’re too wonderful
for anybody
to actually realize you.
Do any human beings
actually realize life while they live it?
Every... Every minute?
Hey, Clara, um...
I know you said
no lame promposals,
but I kind of already started
this before you said that.
So I hope you like it.
(sighs) Clara... I think you
should go to prom with me.
What’s up, dude?
(Clara chuckling) Hey!
(squeals)
(Miller chuckles)
You’re a little preoccupied
with some goats,
but I still think you should
go to prom with me.
Maybe don’t bring the goats.
Those are my goats!
(laughter)
Those are mine.
Clara, I think you
should go to prom with me.
(scoffing) Yeah, right.
Whatever, dude.
(laughter)
(exhales) Okay, so here’s
the thing, Clara Grant.
You just drove by and I know
you saw me standing here.
I do have a girlfriend, but...
all I think about
is you, so...
if you turn around
and offer me a ride,
I’ll take that as a sign
and I’ll break up with my girlfriend
and I’ll eventually
ask you out. But if you don’t...
I’ll just assume
that we weren’t meant to be.
You’re coming back.
(gasps)
Okay, what do you say,
Clara Grant?
Will you go to prom with me?
Of course I will.
Oh... Yay!
Oh, wow.
(applause)
Yay.Oh, yay!
(Lexie) Oh, my goodness!
I should have just
made you a video. (chuckles)
Could have saved us
a lot of time.
It’s so true.
Um...
I am so sorry to interrupt.
Miller, that was adorable.
Thank you, Mrs. Grant.
Do you mind if I steal
your prom date for a second?
(chuckles)
Go ahead.
(Morgan) Oh, my gosh!
I’m not gonna
keep you for long.
I just wanted to say that
watching you on that screen...
Clara, you’re so talented.
And so... fearless.
And I don’t want my fears
to hold you back. Okay?
I want you to follow your passions
wherever they take you.
I want you to ignore
everything and everyone. Even me.
Mostly.(chuckles)
I’m just blown away
by the person you are.
I’m only who I am
because of you.
You got me this far.
(chuckles)
My God,
such a sweet thing to say.
I’m proud of you, too, Mom.
Thank you.
I love you.
Jinx! (chuckles)
Jinx!
(Morgan) Now I’ll make you
buy me a soda
because
it’s a very special day.
I brought
your prom date back.
("Everywhere, Everything"
playing)
(Clara) Got it? No?
(Miller) Yeah. (grunts)
(phone line ringing)
(man) Roman’s Pizza. Will this
be for takeout or delivery?
Uh, delivery.
(chuckles)
Definitely delivery.
(man) All right, sir.
Ready when you are.
What can I get you?
Do you guys
do pineapple on pizza?
(chuckles)
("Everywhere, Everything"
continues playing)
♪ Everywhere, everything ♪
♪ I wanna love you till we’re
Food for the worms to eat ♪
♪ Till our fingers decompose ♪
♪ Keep my hand in yours ♪
♪ Drive slowly ♪
♪ I know every route
In this county ♪
♪ Maybe that ain’t
Such a bad thing ♪
♪ I’ll tell you
Where not to speed ♪
♪ And it’s been a long year ♪
♪ And all of our book’s pages
Dog-eared ♪
♪ We write out the ends
On our palms, dear ♪
♪ Then forget to read ♪
♪ We couldn’t know ♪
♪ That the sun
Was collapsing ♪
♪ Till the seas rose ♪
♪ And the buildings
Came crashing ♪
♪ We cried oh-oh-oh
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Everywhere, everything ♪
♪ I wanna love you till we’re
Food for the worms to eat ♪
♪ Till our fingers decompose ♪
♪ Keep my hand in yours ♪
(song ends)